MUHAMMAD ANAS AFZAAL

B-185 Saghir Centre, Block-16 F.B Area, Karachi.

Phone: +(92)312 3616359 Email: anaskhan.all95@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

<u>Software Developer – ARPATECH (January 2023 – Present)</u>

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of Web Applications.

Technologies & Skills: Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Vuetify, Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Express.js, SQL Server, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Material UI.

Software Developer – AIMVIZ (March 2022 – December 2022)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of Web Applications.

Technologies & Skills: Angular, React.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, ASP.Net Core Web API, SQL Server, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap.

Front end Developer – SYMITS (September 2020 – February 2022)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of static and dynamic websites.

Technologies & Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify and, Adobe Photoshop.

Front end Developer – OPTIMAL CREATIONS (March 2020 –

August 2020)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of static and dynamic websites and content writing for websites and social media marketing.

Technologies & Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify.

SUMMARY

A professional Software Developer having core expertise in the latest Frontend technologies & trends such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.js, Angular, React.js, Nuxt.js, Next.js, jQuery, Material UI, PSD to HTML, PSD to WordPress, and Backend technologies such as Rest APIs, Node.js, Expess.js, and Databases such SQL Server, MongoDB, and Firebase to name a few.

LINKS

Portfolio

LinkedIn.

SKILLS

Next.js:

JavaScript:	
Vue.js:	
Angular:	
React.js:	
TypeScript	
Node.js:	
Express.js:	
REST APIs:	
SQL Server:	
MongoDB:	
React Native:	_
HTML:	
CSS:	
SCSS:	
WordPress:	
jQuery:	

EDUCATION

- Masters of Computer Science (MCS) University of Karachi (2021–2022)
- ➤ Bachelors of Computer Science (BCS) University of Karachi (2016 2019)
- ➤ Intermediate (Pre-Engineering) D.J Science College (2012 2014)
- ➤ Matriculation (Computer Science) Metropolitan Academy (2000 2012)